{"classes":["NAME","DESIGNATION","SKILLS","EMAIL ID","MOBILE NO.","ORG","DATE","GPE","ROLE","LANGUAGES","EDUCATION","HOBBIES","EXPERIENCE","PROJECTS","ADDRESS","ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES","METHODOLOGIES","DOB","COMMUNITY SERVICE","AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"],"annotations":[["Mobile    : +91  96388 11332  \r",{"entities":[[12,28,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["Web  Developer (ASP.NET) ,  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"DESIGNATION"],[16,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["MultiArt Software  \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"ORG"]]}],["Jan  2017   to Current  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"DATE"]]}],["▪ Playing a key role in the design, QA , coding an d maintenance of software systems.  \r",{"entities":[[28,34,"SKILLS"],[36,38,"SKILLS"],[41,47,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Resolve reported fault s in the system and communicate with  testers . \r",{"entities":[[45,56,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Playing a key role in the design, installation, testing,  coding and  maintenance of software \r",{"entities":[[28,34,"SKILLS"],[50,57,"SKILLS"],[60,66,"SKILLS"],[72,83,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Skill : ASP.NET (MVC ), API, SQL SERVER ,JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT,HTML5,BOOTSTRAP ,      \r",{"entities":[[10,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[31,41,"METHODOLOGIES"],[43,49,"METHODOLOGIES"],[51,61,"METHODOLOGIES"],[62,67,"METHODOLOGIES"],[68,77,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["AG  GRID(THRED  PARTY  CONTRAL) . \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Web  Developer (ASP.NET) ,  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["CRMu ltimate  Pvt. Ltd  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Nov 2013 to Dec 2016  \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"DATE"]]}],["▪ Solid experience in using:  Html/Html5,  Asp.Net(C#),CSS . \r",{"entities":[[30,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[43,54,"METHODOLOGIES"],[55,60,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Overseeing direct communications with customers through the CRM.  \r",{"entities":[[62,65,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Developing testing strategies for all aspects of the CRM to en sure the most effective \r",{"entities":[]}],["▪ Skill : ASP.NET (C#),WEB SERVICES, SQL SERVER ,JQUERY, JAVASCRIPT,HTML/HTML5, \r",{"entities":[[10,17,"METHODOLOGIES"],[23,35,"METHODOLOGIES"],[35,47,"METHODOLOGIES"],[49,67,"METHODOLOGIES"],[68,79,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["CSS , TELERIK   CONTROL(THRED  PAR TY  CONTRAL),CRYSTAL  REPORT.  \r",{"entities":[[0,3,"METHODOLOGIES"],[6,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[48,63,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Training  – (B.E. in IT)  \r",{"entities":[[15,25,"EDUCATION"]]}],["            INPTC, Rajkot, India  \r",{"entities":[[12,17,"ORG"],[19,32,"GPE"]]}],["        2012 – 2013  \r",{"entities":[[8,19,"DATE"]]}],["▪ Training  – (B.E. in IT)  \r",{"entities":[[15,25,"EDUCATION"]]}],["              Saurashtra InfoTech  Ltd, Rajkot, India  \r",{"entities":[[14,38,"ORG"],[40,53,"GPE"]]}],["      2012 – 2013  \r",{"entities":[[6,17,"DATE"]]}],["▪ B.E. in C omputer Engineering  \r",{"entities":[[2,31,"EDUCATION"]]}],["      G.K. Bh arad Institute of Engineering  College,  Rajkot,  India  \r",{"entities":[[6,52,"ORG"],[55,69,"GPE"]]}],["                2009 – 2013  \r",{"entities":[[16,27,"DATE"]]}],["▪ Operating systems  WINDOW  UP TO  10,  ANDROID , UNIX,  MAC  \r",{"entities":[[41,48,"SKILLS"],[51,56,"SKILLS"],[58,61,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Programming Languages  ASP.NET(MVC), AG  GRID ,ASP.NET(C#) , JAVA SCRIPT , JQUERY , \r",{"entities":[[25,37,"METHODOLOGIES"],[37,47,"METHODOLOGIES"],[49,60,"METHODOLOGIES"],[63,76,"METHODOLOGIES"],[77,85,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Packages  MS -OFFICE 2010,  2007  ETC . (W ORD , EXCEL , POWER POINT ) \r",{"entities":[[12,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[43,48,"METHODOLOGIES"],[51,56,"METHODOLOGIES"],[59,70,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Graphics  ADOBE CS3,  CS4  ETC . (PHOTOSHOP , INDESIGN ) \r",{"entities":[[2,21,"METHODOLOGIES"],[24,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[36,45,"METHODOLOGIES"],[48,56,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Database Management  SQL  SERVER  2008  TO 2012 ,BASIC AND COMPLEX QUERIES , VIEWS , JOINS , \r",{"entities":[[36,49,"DATE"],[51,76,"METHODOLOGIES"],[87,92,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["▪ Ability to work successfully in a team as a real team player.  \r",{"entities":[[51,62,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Good communication skill.  \r",{"entities":[[2,20,"SKILLS"]]}],["▪ Hones ty, dedication and commitment to work.  \r",{"entities":[]}],[" BINDIYA S   \r",{"entities":[[1,10,"NAME"]]}],["ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER  \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["474,  2nd Cross, 11th Main Indiranagar, Bengaluru -560038  | sbindiya 28@gmail.com  |  9945684919                                                          \r",{"entities":[[0,57,"ADDRESS"],[61,82,"EMAIL ID"],[87,97,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["CMR  institute of technology  \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"ORG"]]}],["201 2-201 6 \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"DATE"]]}],[" BE – Computer science   \r",{"entities":[[1,22,"EDUCATION"]]}],["INSOFE    \r",{"entities":[[0,6,"ORG"]]}],["2017 -2018  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"DATE"]]}],["Post -Graduate program  in Data Science  PROFILE  \r",{"entities":[[0,39,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Passionate software engineer with 3 years of experience \r",{"entities":[[11,28,"DESIGNATION"],[34,41,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["in web application development, focused on writing \r",{"entities":[[3,30,"SKILLS"],[43,50,"SKILLS"]]}],["clean, maintainable, testable codes . Data science \r",{"entities":[[38,50,"SKILLS"]]}],["enthusiast  with experience working on machine learning \r",{"entities":[[39,55,"SKILLS"]]}],["◦ (PROFICIENT)  - JAVA, SPRING \r",{"entities":[[18,30,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["BOOT, JPA, HIBERNATE, \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"METHODOLOGIES"],[6,10,"METHODOLOGIES"],[11,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["JUNIT 5 , PYT HON, DJANGO   \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"],[10,17,"METHODOLOGIES"],[19,25,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ STATISTICS, MACHINE \r",{"entities":[[2,12,"METHODOLOGIES"],[14,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["LEARNING, A RTIFICIAL \r",{"entities":[[10,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["INTELIGENCE, TE NSOR FLOW, \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[13,25,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["PYTORCH  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ COMPUTER VISION , \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["NATURA L LANGU AGE \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["PROCESSING  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ RDBMS – MYSQL, \r",{"entities":[[2,16,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["POSTGRESQL  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ NOSQL – MONGODB  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ AWS CLOUD SERVICES  – \r",{"entities":[[2,20,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["BEANSTALK, FARGATE, SNS, \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"METHODOLOGIES"],[11,18,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["SES, SQS, EC2, RDS, \r",{"entities":[[0,3,"METHODOLOGIES"],[5,8,"METHODOLOGIES"],[10,13,"METHODOLOGIES"],[15,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["PARAMSTORE, CLOUD \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"METHODOLOGIES"],[12,17,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["FORMATION, LAMBDA  \r",{"entities":[[11,17,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ DOCKER  WORK EXPERIENCE  \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Y Media Labs                         Bangalore | 2018 -Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,46,"ORG"],[49,53,"DATE"]]}],["Project: Obie  (Sep 2020 - Present)  \r",{"entities":[[16,34,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["Technology used: Java 11, Spring boot 2, Junit 5 , PostgreSQL, \r",{"entities":[[17,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,39,"METHODOLOGIES"],[41,48,"METHODOLOGIES"],[49,61,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["JPA,  Hibernate,  AWS services, Microservice architecture  \r",{"entities":[[0,3,"METHODOLOGIES"],[6,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[32,57,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["& database design  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"SKILLS"]]}],["maintainable REST API services consumed by mobile \r",{"entities":[[13,30,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Took part in software and architectural development \r",{"entities":[[28,53,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Involved with DevOps team to containerize the \r",{"entities":[[16,22,"SKILLS"]]}],["application with  docker  and deploying an application \r",{"entities":[[18,24,"SKILLS"]]}],["using  AWS Fargate   \r",{"entities":[[7,18,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Implemented Recommendation  engine  to recommend  \r",{"entities":[[14,36,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["user specific content using cosi ne similarity  \r",{"entities":[[28,46,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ IDE – INTELIJ , PYCHARM  \r",{"entities":[[8,15,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,25,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ OTHER TOOLS – POSTMAN  \r",{"entities":[[16,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["◦ CI/CD PROCESS - JENKINS  Project: Wat ani  (Oct 201 8 – May 2020)  \r",{"entities":[[46,55,"DATE"],[58,66,"DATE"]]}],["Technology used: Java 8, Spring boot 2, JPA, Hibernate, AWS \r",{"entities":[[17,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,38,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,55,"METHODOLOGIES"],[56,59,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["services (Beanstalk, Lambda, SNS, SQS, SES, Cloud watch ) \r",{"entities":[[10,19,"METHODOLOGIES"],[21,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[34,37,"METHODOLOGIES"],[39,42,"METHODOLOGIES"],[44,55,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["During PGP in Data Scienc e \r",{"entities":[[7,27,"EDUCATION"]]}],["using mul tiple liner regression and imported attributes \r",{"entities":[[6,32,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["derived using EDA and recursive feature elimination \r",{"entities":[[14,17,"METHODOLOGIES"],[22,51,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["w.r.t step AIC and VIF using Cooks’ D  \r",{"entities":[[11,14,"METHODOLOGIES"],[19,22,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,37,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Implemented grid search CV to make the model \r",{"entities":[[14,28,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["and logistics regression , time series analysis , ridge \r",{"entities":[[27,47,"METHODOLOGIES"],[50,55,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["and lasso regression, naive Bayes  model, ensemble \r",{"entities":[[4,20,"METHODOLOGIES"],[22,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[42,50,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["models – Bagging , boosting , st acking, support vector \r",{"entities":[[0,6,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[19,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[30,39,"METHODOLOGIES"],[41,55,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["machine and lazy lear ner  (KNN )  \r",{"entities":[[12,33,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Gained familiarity with Unsupervised Learning \r",{"entities":[[26,47,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Algorithms like  Associati on Rule, Clustering, Principal \r",{"entities":[[17,34,"METHODOLOGIES"],[36,47,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Component A nalysis (PCA) Text Analytics  and \r",{"entities":[[20,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,40,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Recommendation Engine  \r",{"entities":[[0,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Computer Vision  \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Resolved all problems based on Plant Pathology using \r",{"entities":[[33,48,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Base M odel CNN Architecture with an accuracy of 60 % \r",{"entities":[[12,28,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Gained k nowledge o f Convolutional Neural Networks \r",{"entities":[[24,53,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Models (Image C lass ification, Segmentation) using \r",{"entities":[[8,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[32,44,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Keras  \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Natural Language Processing  \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Resolved p roblems on sentiment analysis and \r",{"entities":[[24,42,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["classification s using TF-IDF V ectors with an accuracy of \r",{"entities":[[23,38,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["STAR AWARD ” FOR \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],["Divya Prabhakar Jathan  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"NAME"]]}],["Email -divyajathan28@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[6,30,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["                                                                    Contact No -7410100319  \r",{"entities":[[79,90,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["Address -502/C -Wing,  Sai leela Apartment,  Vinay complex, Nalasopara (West)  \r",{"entities":[[8,77,"ADDRESS"]]}],["A) Illusion Dental Laboratory Private Limited : - Worked as Credit Control Executive with \r",{"entities":[[3,45,"ORG"],[60,84,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["total experience of 10 Months  (From July 2017 to April 2018) . \r",{"entities":[[20,29,"EXPERIENCE"],[37,46,"DATE"],[50,61,"DATE"]]}],["B) HDB Financial Service Private Limited : - Worked as senior Tele Caller (Loan against \r",{"entities":[[3,40,"ORG"],[55,73,"ORG"]]}],["Property) department, with total Work Experience of 1 year  (From March 2016 to March \r",{"entities":[[52,58,"EXPERIENCE"],[66,76,"DATE"]]}],["2017) . \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"DATE"]]}],["Standard  University  School/college  Year of \r",{"entities":[[0,36,"ORG"]]}],["SSC  Mumbai University  Cardinal Gracias High school  2009  49%  \r",{"entities":[[0,52,"ORG"]]}],["HSC  Mumbai University  Chetana college of Arts  & \r",{"entities":[[0,47,"ORG"]]}],["T.Y.B.COM  Mumbai University  Chetana college of Arts  & \r",{"entities":[[11,53,"ORG"]]}],["commerce  2014  60%  \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"]]}],["M.COM Part -1 Mumbai University  Mumbai University  Cleared   \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"EDUCATION"]]}],["52%  M.COM PART -2 Mumbai University  Mumbai University  Cleared  \r",{"entities":[[5,10,"EDUCATION"],[19,36,"ORG"]]}],[" Excellent   Communications Skills  \r",{"entities":[[2,35,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Customer Relationship Management.   \r",{"entities":[[2,35,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Positive attitude towards work  \r",{"entities":[[2,32,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Hardworking and dedicated  \r",{"entities":[[2,13,"SKILLS"],[18,27,"SKILLS"]]}],[" MS Excel  \r",{"entities":[[2,10,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Ms Word  \r",{"entities":[[2,9,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Basics Of Tally  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"SKILLS"]]}],["Date o f Birth : - 13th June,  1993  \r",{"entities":[[19,35,"DOB"]]}],["Language   Known : - English, Hindi, Marathi, Tulu  \r",{"entities":[[21,28,"LANGUAGES"],[30,35,"LANGUAGES"],[37,44,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["DINESHKUMAR DHANASEKAR  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"NAME"]]}],["S E N I O R  S O F T W A R E  D E V E L O P E R  \r",{"entities":[[0,47,"DESIGNATION"]]}],[" P  +91 -9940233643   E  Dinesh96.dk@gmail.com   A  19/10, Ramasamy \r",{"entities":[[4,19,"MOBILE NO."],[25,46,"EMAIL ID"],[52,67,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Garden Street,  Adyar, \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Chennai - 600020   In  www.linkedin.com/in/dine\r",{"entities":[[0,16,"ADDRESS"]]}],["• Qualified Full Stack Web Developer with 3+ years of experience \r",{"entities":[[12,36,"DESIGNATION"],[42,50,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["in python programming and strong knowledge of frontend \r",{"entities":[[3,21,"SKILLS"]]}],["requirements.  \r",{"entities":[]}],["• Highly effective at analyzing existing systems to discover issues \r",{"entities":[[22,31,"SKILLS"]]}],[" • B.E. COMPUTER SCIENCE \r",{"entities":[[3,24,"EDUCATION"]]}],["2017)  AGNI COLLEGE OF \r",{"entities":[[7,19,"EDUCATION"]]}],["TECHNOLOGY  , CHENNAI, \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"GPE"]]}],["TAMIL NADU  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["• PROGRAMMING \r",{"entities":[[2,13,"SKILLS"]]}],["LANGUAGES:  PYTHON 2.7+,  \r",{"entities":[[12,24,"SKILLS"]]}],["3+, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, \r",{"entities":[[4,14,"SKILLS"],[16,23,"SKILLS"]]}],["HTML5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP  \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"METHODOLOGIES"],[7,10,"METHODOLOGIES"],[12,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• FRAMEWORKS: ANGULAR \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["2+, IONIC , DJANGO  \r",{"entities":[[4,9,"METHODOLOGIES"],[12,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• ERP SOFTWARES:  ODOO  \r",{"entities":[[2,15,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• DATABASES:  POSTGRESQL  \r",{"entities":[[14,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• CHART S: CHART JS, \r",{"entities":[[11,20,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["ECHARTS, D3  \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• IDE TOOLS:  ECLIPSE , VISUAL \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• VERSION CONTROLS:  GIT \r",{"entities":[[21,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["AND SVN  \r",{"entities":[[4,7,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["WINDOWS 7/8/10 , LINUX  \r",{"entities":[[17,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Aug 2020  - Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,19,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["Senior Software Developer • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,25,"DESIGNATION"],[28,47,"ORG"],[49,56,"GPE"]]}],["Global Time Tracking System (GTS) (Aug 2021 –Present):  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"],[34,52,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["• Environm ent :  Python, Odoo, JQuery, HTML, PostgreSQL  \r",{"entities":[[18,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[32,44,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,56,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["T & E  for Neveda Gaming Control Board  (May 2021  – Present ): \r",{"entities":[[0,38,"ORG"],[41,49,"DATE"]]}],["Application Tracking System (ATS) ( Nov 2019 – Apr 2021):  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"METHODOLOGIES"],[36,44,"DATE"],[47,55,"DATE"]]}],["Jul 2019 – Jul 2020  \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"DATE"],[11,19,"DATE"]]}],["Software Engineer  • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"DESIGNATION"],[21,40,"ORG"],[42,49,"GPE"]]}],["Sales Office CRM ( Apr 2019 – Aug 2019):  \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"DESIGNATION"],[19,27,"DATE"],[30,38,"DATE"]]}],["• Sales Office is a multi -company CRM tool that helps business to \r",{"entities":[[35,38,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Mar  2018 – Jul 2019  \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"DATE"],[12,20,"DATE"]]}],["Program Analyst Trainee • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"DESIGNATION"],[26,45,"ORG"],[47,54,"GPE"]]}],["Dynamic Dashboard Application ( Dec 2018 – Jul 2019):  \r",{"entities":[[0,29,"PROJECTS"],[32,40,"DATE"],[43,51,"DATE"]]}],["• Environment :  Django, Python, Odoo, JQuery, Postgr es, Charts  \r",{"entities":[[17,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,31,"METHODOLOGIES"],[33,37,"METHODOLOGIES"],[39,45,"METHODOLOGIES"],[47,56,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Training Request ( Aug 2018 – Nov 2018):  \r",{"entities":[[19,27,"DATE"],[30,38,"DATE"]]}],["Data Quality Check ( May 2018 – Aug 2018):  \r",{"entities":[[21,29,"DATE"],[32,40,"DATE"]]}],["• EXTRA MILER AWARD  – \r",{"entities":[[2,19,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],["Q2, 2020 FOR EXCELLENCE IN \r",{"entities":[[4,8,"DATE"]]}],["IMPLEMENTATION OF ATS \r",{"entities":[]}],["• DOB : JUN 9, 1996  \r",{"entities":[[8,19,"DOB"]]}],["• LANGUAGES:  TAMIL AND \r",{"entities":[[14,19,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["ENGLISH  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["• TAMIL POETRY  \r",{"entities":[[2,14,"HOBBIES"]]}],["Dushyant Singh  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"NAME"]]}],["Full Stack Product Developer   \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Bangalore, India  \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["+91 -9782113770  \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["DushyantChouhan63@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["on experience in Angular 2,6,7, C#, .Net Core, Web API , Type Script, SQL Server, HTML , \r",{"entities":[[17,31,"SKILLS"],[32,33,"SKILLS"],[36,45,"SKILLS"],[47,54,"SKILLS"],[57,68,"SKILLS"],[70,80,"METHODOLOGIES"],[82,88,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["AWS (Dynamo Db), JavaScript, Analytics ( MS Power BI ) having 4.5+ yrs. experience in Web \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"SKILLS"],[17,27,"SKILLS"],[29,38,"SKILLS"],[41,52,"SKILLS"],[62,71,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["Application & Product Development , Data Migration and Product  Implementation . \r",{"entities":[[14,33,"SKILLS"],[36,50,"SKILLS"],[55,78,"SKILLS"]]}],["Apart from technical skills, he is a team player with positive attitude having excellent \r",{"entities":[[37,48,"SKILLS"]]}],["communication skills, quick learning skills , strong analytical skills  and Problem -solving \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"SKILLS"],[22,43,"SKILLS"],[46,70,"SKILLS"],[76,92,"SKILLS"]]}],["Angular 6,7 , TypeScript  Problem Solving & Data Analysis Skills \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"SKILLS"],[14,41,"SKILLS"],[44,57,"SKILLS"]]}],["C#, .Net Core , Web  API, AWS  Analytical & Logical Reasoning Skills \r",{"entities":[[14,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,68,"SKILLS"]]}],["HTML , JavaScript  & CSS  Quick Learning  Skills  \r",{"entities":[[21,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,40,"SKILLS"]]}],["T – SQL (MS SQL Server  2012,  2014)  Excellent Communication skills \r",{"entities":[[4,7,"SKILLS"]]}],["Visual Studio, Git, Code Commit, MSBI Presentation Skills & MS  Excel  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"SKILLS"],[15,18,"SKILLS"],[20,31,"SKILLS"],[33,57,"SKILLS"]]}],["Apr 2019 – till present  \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"DATE"]]}],["Dec 2016 – Apr 2019  \r",{"entities":[[0,19,"DATE"]]}],["Sr. Software Developer  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["• Well  versed  in Coding  & Unit  testing  by following  Agile  (Scrum)  methodology.  \r",{"entities":[[58,85,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Hands on exp.  in Angular  6,7, C# .Net  Core , Web  API , AWS, Dynamo Db,  \r",{"entities":[[66,75,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Code Commit , HTML,  CSS , SQL Server, Git and Visual Studio.  \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[14,18,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Associate Professional Product Developer, R & D Dept.  \r",{"entities":[[0,40,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["• Hands on in C# .Net, SQL, Web API, Asp.Net , Entity Framework,  LINQ, \r",{"entities":[[37,44,"METHODOLOGIES"],[66,70,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Ado.Net, MS Power BI, JavaScript, Angular 2 and  HTML.  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,20,"METHODOLOGIES"],[22,32,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Mar 2016 - Dec 2016  Programmer, Base Aviation Product Development Dept.  \r",{"entities":[[21,31,"DESIGNATION"],[33,46,"ORG"]]}],["• Developed an Automation tool from Scratch using C#, .Net  Framework.  \r",{"entities":[[54,69,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Ramco Systems Ltd.  \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"ORG"]]}],["UST Global India Ltd.  \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"]]}],["DXC Technology Ltd.  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"]]}],["Apr  2019 - Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"DATE"]]}],["• Coding, U nit testing of  User Stories to resolve complex business  requirements.  \r",{"entities":[[10,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Handling Code reviews, Code Merge and Production Deployment  support . \r",{"entities":[[2,23,"SKILLS"],[25,39,"SKILLS"],[40,70,"SKILLS"]]}],["Web API , LINQ , Entity Framework, Angular, JavaScript, HTML and XML by \r",{"entities":[[10,14,"METHODOLOGIES"],[17,33,"METHODOLOGIES"],[44,54,"METHODOLOGIES"],[56,68,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["following Agile Methodologies.  \r",{"entities":[[10,29,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["2. Achieved  Pat on the Back  award by client ( FAI ) for complex  user  stor ies. \r",{"entities":[[3,35,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],["Bachelor of Technology (ECE) – Rajasthan Technical University, 2015  \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"EDUCATION"],[31,61,"ORG"],[63,67,"DATE"]]}],["• Undergone Higher Sec. Education with PCM & C++, scored 1st  divisi on. \r",{"entities":[[12,33,"EDUCATION"]]}],["UST Global India Ltd.  \r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"]]}],["DXC Technology Ltd.  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"]]}],["  PRODYOT CHATTERJEE  \r",{"entities":[[2,20,"NAME"]]}],["Phone : +91 -9830832962 | E-Mail: prodyot4u@yahoo.co.in  \r",{"entities":[[8,23,"MOBILE NO."],[34,55,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["A profound professional with over 12 years of experience in Strategy Planning, Profit Centre Operations, Sustainability, \r",{"entities":[[34,42,"EXPERIENCE"],[60,77,"SKILLS"],[79,103,"SKILLS"]]}],["New Business & Client Acquisition, Branding & Marketing, Channel & Distribution Management and Team Management  \r",{"entities":[[15,33,"SKILLS"],[46,55,"SKILLS"],[57,90,"SKILLS"],[95,110,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Developing marketing plans t o build consumer preference through in -depth understanding of markets & city dynamics  \r",{"entities":[[2,28,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Evolving market segmentation & penetration st rategies to achieve targets  \r",{"entities":[[11,44,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Impressive communicator with honed interpersonal, team building, negotiation, presentation, convincing & analytical skills  \r",{"entities":[[2,25,"SKILLS"],[52,65,"SKILLS"],[67,78,"SKILLS"],[94,104,"SKILLS"]]}],["OCS Group (India) Pvt . Ltd., Kolkata          Since Mar’13  \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"ORG"],[30,37,"GPE"],[53,59,"DATE"]]}],["DGM – Business development (East Zone)  \r",{"entities":[[0,3,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["• Managing selection, negotiation and execution of service associates or vendor  \r",{"entities":[[22,33,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Directing preparation of proposals, planning, transition team management and cross -functional liaising & coordination \r",{"entities":[[38,46,"SKILLS"],[79,105,"SKILLS"]]}],["along with managing Brand Promotion through  different activities  \r",{"entities":[[20,35,"SKILLS"]]}],["Cummins India Ltd.            May’11 – Mar’13  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[30,36,"DATE"],[39,45,"DATE"]]}],["Manager – Service Solutions (East Zone)  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DESIGNATION"],[10,27,"ORG"]]}],["• Adeptly  managed  all aspects  of power generation business (from 7.5 KVA to 3000 KVA ) especially managing service solutions \r",{"entities":[[101,127,"SKILLS"]]}],["M/s . Absotherm Services (P) Ltd.,  Kolkata  (India )        Apr’06 – May’11  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"],[36,53,"GPE"],[61,67,"DATE"]]}],["Asst. Manager – Business Development (East India)  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Jr. Executive – Business Development         Apr’06 – July’08  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"DESIGNATION"],[45,51,"DATE"],[54,61,"DATE"]]}],["Sr. Executive – Business Development         July’08  – Aug’09  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"DESIGNATION"],[45,52,"DATE"],[56,62,"DATE"]]}],["Asst. Manager – Business Development         Aug’09  – May’11  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"DESIGNATION"],[45,51,"DATE"],[55,61,"DATE"]]}],["Asst. Manager – Business Development  (newly named as  Absotherm Facility Management (P) Ltd. ) Aug’09 – May’11  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"DESIGNATION"],[55,93,"ORG"],[96,102,"DATE"],[105,111,"DATE"]]}],["on offer with entry and complete business set up in Kolkata, Ranchi, Patna, Jamshedpur and Bhubaneswar  \r",{"entities":[[52,59,"GPE"],[61,67,"GPE"],[69,74,"GPE"],[74,86,"GPE"],[91,102,"GPE"]]}],["• Meticulously  explored and acquired  key accounts like The Grand Oberoi, Hyatt Regency, Unitech Group, Infinity IT and The \r",{"entities":[[57,73,"ORG"],[75,88,"ORG"],[90,103,"ORG"],[105,116,"ORG"]]}],["• Established tie-up’s & relations for  being preferred bu siness partners for CBRE, JLLM and Peninsula F acility Management  \r",{"entities":[[85,89,"ORG"],[94,124,"ORG"]]}],["ICICI Bank Ltd.,  Kolkata           Oct’0 4 – Apr’06  \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"ORG"],[18,25,"GPE"],[36,43,"DATE"],[46,52,"DATE"]]}],["Sales Executive –Retail Asset Division  \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["• Operated as  In-charge of Sales & Marketing ac tivities for  retail sales of two -wheeler loan,  credit card and personal loans  \r",{"entities":[[28,45,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Master of Business Management from National Institute of Business Management, Chennai  in 2008  \r",{"entities":[[2,31,"EDUCATION"],[37,78,"ORG"],[80,87,"GPE"],[92,96,"DATE"]]}],["• B.A.  (English) from University of Calcutta in the year 2000  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"EDUCATION"],[23,45,"ORG"],[58,62,"DATE"]]}],["Date of Birth:   20th  June 1980  \r",{"entities":[[17,32,"DOB"]]}],["Languages Known:  English, Hindi and Bengali  \r",{"entities":[[18,25,"LANGUAGES"],[27,32,"LANGUAGES"],[37,44,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["Address:   8, P.K. Guha Road, 4/A, Debangshee Apartment, Dum Dum Cantonment – 700028, Kolkata   \r",{"entities":[[11,93,"ADDRESS"]]}],["DINESHKUMAR DHANASEKAR  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"NAME"]]}],["S E N I O R  S O F T W A R E  D E V E L O P E R  \r",{"entities":[[0,47,"DESIGNATION"]]}],[" P  +91 -9940233643   E  Dinesh96.dk@gmail.com   A  19/10, Ramasamy \r",{"entities":[[4,19,"MOBILE NO."],[25,46,"EMAIL ID"],[52,67,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Garden Street,  Adyar, \r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Chennai - 600020   In  www.linkedin.com/in/dine\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["• Qualified Full Stack Web Developer with 3+ years of experience \r",{"entities":[[12,36,"DESIGNATION"],[42,50,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["in python programming and strong knowledge of frontend \r",{"entities":[[3,21,"SKILLS"]]}],[" • B.E. COMPUTER SCIENCE \r",{"entities":[[3,24,"EDUCATION"]]}],["2017)  AGNI COLLEGE OF \r",{"entities":[[7,19,"ORG"]]}],["TECHNOLOGY  , CHENNAI, \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"GPE"]]}],["TAMIL NADU  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["• PROGRAMMING \r",{"entities":[[2,13,"SKILLS"]]}],["LANGUAGES:  PYTHON 2.7+,  \r",{"entities":[[12,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["3+, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, \r",{"entities":[[4,14,"METHODOLOGIES"],[16,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["HTML5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP  \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"METHODOLOGIES"],[7,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[12,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• FRAMEWORKS: ANGULAR \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["2+, IONIC , DJANGO  \r",{"entities":[[4,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[12,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• ERP SOFTWARES:  ODOO  \r",{"entities":[[18,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• DATABASES:  POSTGRESQL  \r",{"entities":[[14,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• CHART S: CHART JS, \r",{"entities":[[11,20,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["ECHARTS, D3  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,11,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• IDE TOOLS:  ECLIPSE , VISUAL \r",{"entities":[[14,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["STUDIO CODE  \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• VERSION CONTROLS:  GIT \r",{"entities":[[21,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["AND SVN  \r",{"entities":[[4,7,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["WINDOWS 7/8/10 , LINUX  \r",{"entities":[[17,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Senior Software Developer • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,25,"DESIGNATION"],[28,47,"ORG"],[49,56,"GPE"]]}],["Global Time Tracking System (GTS) (Aug 2021 –Present):  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"]]}],["expenses  for all the group of companies under HTC . \r",{"entities":[[47,50,"ORG"]]}],["• Environm ent :  Python, Odoo, JQuery, HTML, PostgreSQL  \r",{"entities":[[32,38,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,44,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,56,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["T & E  for Neveda Gaming Control Board  (May 2021  – Present ): \r",{"entities":[[0,38,"ORG"]]}],["Application Tracking System (ATS) ( Nov 2019 – Apr 2021):  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"METHODOLOGIES"],[36,44,"DATE"],[47,55,"DATE"]]}],["• Developed forms, dashboards and defined flow for candidate  \r",{"entities":[[19,29,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Jul 2019 – Jul 2020  \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"DATE"],[11,19,"DATE"]]}],["Software Engineer  • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"DESIGNATION"],[21,40,"ORG"],[42,49,"GPE"]]}],["Program Analyst Trainee • HTC Global Services, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"DESIGNATION"],[26,45,"ORG"],[45,54,"GPE"]]}],["functionalities with mult iple data visualization options.  \r",{"entities":[[36,49,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Environment :  Django, Python, Odoo, JQuery, Postgr es, Charts  \r",{"entities":[[17,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Environment :  Python, Odoo, PostgreSQL , Linux   \r",{"entities":[[23,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,41,"METHODOLOGIES"],[42,49,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• EXTRA MILER AWARD  – \r",{"entities":[[2,19,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],["AWARD  FOR SOLVED 40+ \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],["• DOB : JUN 9, 1996  \r",{"entities":[[8,19,"DOB"]]}],["• LANGUAGES:  TAMIL AND \r",{"entities":[[14,19,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["ENGLISH  \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["• COIN COLLECTION  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"HOBBIES"]]}],["• TAMIL POETRY  \r",{"entities":[[2,14,"HOBBIES"]]}],["gomathimanik9792@gmail.com \r",{"entities":[[0,26,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["   9600967003\r",{"entities":[[4,14,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["   841,A/4, anna nagar , EB\r",{"entities":[[4,23,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Colony , Nor th gandhigr amam \r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Understanding of fr ont-end\r",{"entities":[[17,27,"SKILLS"]]}],["technologies (React js,\r",{"entities":[[14,22,"SKILLS"]]}],["JavaScript, H TML5, CSS3)\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"SKILLS"],[12,18,"SKILLS"],[20,24,"SKILLS"]]}],["Effectiv e communication skills\r",{"entities":[[0,31,"SKILLS"]]}],["Analytical skills\r",{"entities":[[0,17,"SKILLS"]]}],["Interpersonal and teamwork skills CAREER OBJEC TIVE\r",{"entities":[[0,26,"SKILLS"]]}],["Omega healthcar e\r",{"entities":[[0,17,"ORG"]]}],["Project suppor t\r",{"entities":[[0,16,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["28th No v 2018  - 31st Dec 2021\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"DATE"],[18,31,"DATE"]]}],["Coding pr oject suppor t ex ecutiv e\r",{"entities":[[0,36,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["SEE TH ALAKSHMI RAM ASW AM Y COLLEGE, TRICH Y\r",{"entities":[[0,36,"ORG"],[38,45,"GPE"]]}],["BCA\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"EDUCATION"]]}],[" 2017\r",{"entities":[[1,5,"DATE"]]}],["SRI VID YA M ANDIR M ATRIC HR SEC SCHOOL,\r",{"entities":[[0,40,"ORG"]]}],["THURAI YUR\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["HSC\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"EDUCATION"]]}],["SRI VID YA M ANDIR M ATRIC HR SEC SCHOOL,\r",{"entities":[[0,40,"ORG"]]}],["THURAI YUR\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["Diplomo in Information technology\r",{"entities":[[0,33,"EDUCATION"]]}],["English lower le vel typewriting\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"LANGUAGES"],[21,32,"SKILLS"]]}],["Date of Bir th :23/02/1997\r",{"entities":[[15,26,"DOB"]]}],["Known Languages :TAMIL, ENGLISH\r",{"entities":[[17,22,"LANGUAGES"],[24,31,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["JAVIYA ASH A \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"NAME"]]}],["SKILL OF BBA STUDEN TS (F .Y, \r",{"entities":[[9,12,"EDUCATION"]]}],["   Asha.1.ja viya@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[4,28,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["   9512301219\r",{"entities":[[4,14,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["   B/401, BL UE BELL BUILDING, \r",{"entities":[[4,31,"ADDRESS"]]}],["         RO YAL COMPLEX, EKSAR  \r",{"entities":[[9,30,"ADDRESS"]]}],["         BORIV ALI WEST , MUMBAI -  \r",{"entities":[[9,32,"ADDRESS"]]}],["ENGLISH GRAMM AR\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["READING\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"HOBBIES"]]}],["GAJERA P ATEL SANKUL , AMRELI\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"NAME"]]}],["LEC TURER OF COMMUNICA TION SKILL OF BBA STUDEN TS \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["6/6/2016  - 01/11/2017\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"DATE"],[12,22,"DATE"]]}],["31-01-2018  - 12-01-2019\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"DATE"],[14,24,"DATE"]]}],["GUJ ARA T UNIVERSI TY\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"DATE"]]}],["MASTER OF AR TS\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"EDUCATION"]]}],["SA URASH TRA UNIVERSI TY\r",{"entities":[[0,24,"ORG"]]}],["BA CHEL OR OF AR TS\r",{"entities":[[0,19,"EDUCATION"]]}],[" MARCH - 2014\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"DATE"]]}],["HSC\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"EDUCATION"]]}],[" MARCH - 2011\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"DATE"]]}],["SSC\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Date of Bir th :20/10/1993\r",{"entities":[[15,26,"DOB"]]}],["Known Languages :ENGLISH, HINDI, GUJ ARA TI\r",{"entities":[[17,24,"LANGUAGES"],[26,31,"LANGUAGES"],[33,43,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["Hobb y :READING\r",{"entities":[[8,15,"HOBBIES"]]}],["Professional  Snapshot  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Anjali  Singh  \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"NAME"]]}],["Email:   singh.anji2161@gmail.com  Mobile:  +91  6304502404  \r",{"entities":[[9,33,"EMAIL ID"],[44,59,"MOBILE NO."]]}],[" 3.8+ years  of IT experience  which  includes  the  experience  in developing  User  Interface  (UI)  \r",{"entities":[[2,12,"EXPERIENCE"],[81,102,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["applications  using  HTML,  CSS,  Bootstrap  5, JAVASCRIPT, JSON,  Angular  2+.  \r",{"entities":[[21,25,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,31,"METHODOLOGIES"],[34,46,"METHODOLOGIES"],[48,58,"METHODOLOGIES"],[60,64,"METHODOLOGIES"],[67,78,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Knowledge  in Managing  Project  Source Code  using  GitHub,  Bitbucket,  Azure  DevOps,  Git  Bash.  \r",{"entities":[[55,61,"METHODOLOGIES"],[64,73,"METHODOLOGIES"],[76,89,"METHODOLOGIES"],[92,101,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Experience  in developing  single  page  applications  (SPA)  using  Angular.  \r",{"entities":[[29,62,"SKILLS"],[71,78,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Implemented  bootstrap  CSS  for  developing  rich  and  responsive  UI.  \r",{"entities":[[15,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[59,73,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Knowledge  on client -side scripting  and  JavaScript  frameworks.  \r",{"entities":[[16,38,"SKILLS"],[45,67,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Working  as Software  Developer  at Sun  Icon  Systems,  Hyderabad  since  May  2018  to present.  \r",{"entities":[[38,56,"DESIGNATION"],[77,86,"DATE"]]}],[" Bachelor of Engineering – 2016 from GNIOT Gr.Noida  (Uttar Pradesh), Affiliated by Dr. A.P.J. Abdul  \r",{"entities":[[2,25,"EDUCATION"],[28,32,"DATE"],[38,43,"ORG"],[44,52,"GPE"],[55,68,"GPE"],[85,101,"NAME"]]}],[" Intermediate  – 2011  from  R.K.M.S  (Jamshedpur),  Affiliated  by I.S.C  with  65%  \r",{"entities":[[18,22,"DATE"],[40,50,"GPE"]]}],[" Programming  Languages  C \r",{"entities":[[26,27,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Web  Technologies  HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AJAX, JSON, TypeScript  \r",{"entities":[[21,26,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,56,"METHODOLOGIES"],[57,61,"METHODOLOGIES"],[63,67,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" IDE/Tools  Visual  Code  Studio,  Visual  Studio  \r",{"entities":[[36,50,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Tools  NPM,  GitHub  \r",{"entities":[[9,12,"METHODOLOGIES"],[15,21,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Good  Communication  Skills  and  Excellent  Learning  Skills  with  specified  time  period.  \r",{"entities":[[2,21,"SKILLS"],[36,55,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Excellent  decision -making  skills  and  Ability  to work  under  pressure  and  accept  new  challenges.  \r",{"entities":[[44,77,"SKILLS"],[84,107,"SKILLS"]]}],["Commitment,  Dedication  and  excellent  Analytical,  Programming  and  efficient  Problems  Solving  skills.  \r",{"entities":[[83,108,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Self -motivated  and  fast  learner  with  strong  interpersonal  and  communication  skills.  \r",{"entities":[[2,17,"SKILLS"],[24,37,"SKILLS"]]}],["Role  UI Developer  \r",{"entities":[[6,18,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Organization  Sun  Icon  Systems  \r",{"entities":[[14,32,"ORG"]]}],["Duration  Since February,  2020 to  Till  Date  \r",{"entities":[[16,31,"DATE"]]}],["Environment  Languages:  TypeScript,  HTML5,  CSS3,  Boostrap4,  Angular  10,  D3 Chart  \r",{"entities":[[38,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,51,"METHODOLOGIES"],[62,76,"METHODOLOGIES"],[79,81,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Also  involve  on bugs  fixing  and  performance  improvement  of the  existing  programs.  \r",{"entities":[[20,32,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Deployment  of Project  Build  using  Azure  cloud  service.  \r",{"entities":[[40,61,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Role  Team  Member  \r",{"entities":[[6,18,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Organization  Sun  Icon  Systems  \r",{"entities":[[14,32,"ORG"]]}],["Duration  Since October,  2018  to Jan  2020  \r",{"entities":[[16,30,"DATE"],[35,44,"DATE"]]}],[" After  Design  Document  approval,  design,  Web/UI  development  of the  Application  using  HTML,  \r",{"entities":[[38,44,"SKILLS"],[47,66,"SKILLS"]]}],["PLACE:  Hyderabad  Name:  Anjali  Singh  Organizational  Experience  \r",{"entities":[[8,17,"GPE"],[26,39,"NAME"]]}],["Address: 1/85, Pillaiyar kovil street,\r",{"entities":[[9,37,"ADDRESS"]]}],["KonganthanParai, Tirunelveli.\r",{"entities":[[0,28,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Email: arumugadurga@gmail.comCONTACT M E AT\r",{"entities":[[7,36,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["CSS, jquery, Tailwind CSS\r",{"entities":[[5,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[13,25,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Database: Mongo Db, Airtable\r",{"entities":[[10,18,"METHODOLOGIES"],[20,28,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Amazon Web Services:  AWS API\r",{"entities":[[22,29,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Gateway, Cognito, Lambda, EC2,\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,30,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Dynamo DbFramework: Node js, Vue js, Nuxt js,\r",{"entities":[[20,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,35,"METHODOLOGIES"],[37,44,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Object Oriented Programming\r",{"entities":[[0,27,"SKILLS"]]}],["Protocols: Rest, HTTP, UDP, TCPArchitecture: Microservice\r",{"entities":[[11,15,"METHODOLOGIES"],[17,21,"METHODOLOGIES"],[23,26,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,57,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Architecture, Monolithic\r",{"entities":[[12,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Architect, Design, Development, Deployment, Test the Product\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"SKILLS"],[9,17,"SKILLS"],[19,30,"SKILLS"],[32,42,"SKILLS"],[44,60,"SKILLS"]]}],["development Process.Teezle Telematics India Pvt Ltd\r",{"entities":[[27,51,"ORG"]]}],["Full Stack Developer | Aug 2018 - Mar  2021, ChennaiPERSONAL PROFILE\r",{"entities":[[0,20,"DESIGNATION"],[23,31,"DATE"],[34,43,"DATE"]]}],["I am a Full Stack Developer  with 3+ years of experience and\r",{"entities":[[7,27,"DESIGNATION"],[34,42,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["Achievement-driven professional with an experience of 3+\r",{"entities":[[54,56,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["years in IoT Product Company to develop SaaS and PaaS\r",{"entities":[[40,44,"SKILLS"],[49,53,"SKILLS"]]}],["Involved in Analysis, Architect, Design, Develop(full stack)\r",{"entities":[[12,20,"SKILLS"],[22,31,"SKILLS"],[33,39,"SKILLS"],[41,48,"SKILLS"]]}],["Development Tools:  WebStrom,\r",{"entities":[[20,28,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Visual Studio code, Bitbucket\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"METHODOLOGIES"],[20,29,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Logging Tools: Sumologic, MixpanelPhone : 7373860277, 6374123348\r",{"entities":[[15,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[42,52,"MOBILE NO."],[54,64,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["Architect, Design, Development, Deployment, Test the\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"SKILLS"],[11,17,"SKILLS"],[19,30,"SKILLS"],[32,42,"SKILLS"]]}],["Product and Support after Product release in Agile Process.Hash8.IO Pvt Ltd\r",{"entities":[[68,75,"ORG"]]}],["Full Stack Developer | Mar 2021 - Sep 2021, Hosur\r",{"entities":[[0,20,"DESIGNATION"],[23,31,"DATE"],[34,42,"DATE"],[44,49,"GPE"]]}],["IAM Tools: Autho, Cognito\r",{"entities":[[11,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,25,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Fleet Management System\r",{"entities":[[0,23,"SKILLS"]]}],["                 This is a IoT application of small and large scale fleet to\r",{"entities":[[27,42,"SKILLS"]]}],["Product Management Tools: Jira, \r",{"entities":[[26,30,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Clockify, Basecamp\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"METHODOLOGIES"],[10,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["UI/UX Design: Canva\r",{"entities":[[14,19,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Technologies: Snowflake, Container,\r",{"entities":[[14,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,34,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Docker, Kubernetes, Basic \r",{"entities":[[0,6,"METHODOLOGIES"],[8,18,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Completed B.E in Electrical and Electronics Engineering at\r",{"entities":[[10,55,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Completed Higher Secondary School at St.Ignatius' Convent\r",{"entities":[[10,33,"EDUCATION"],[37,57,"ORG"]]}],["Completed Secondary School Leaving Certificate at\r",{"entities":[[10,26,"EDUCATION"]]}],["St.Ignatius' Convent with 92%.       Einstein college of Engineering with 8.6 CGPA.\r",{"entities":[[37,68,"ORG"]]}],["Anup Sagar Singh \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"NAME"]]}],["Senior Engineer \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["anupsagarsingh@gmail.com \r",{"entities":[[0,24,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["+91-9901039364 \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["Bengaluru, India \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Big Data Analytics, Postgraduate Degree \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"SKILLS"],[20,39,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Indian Institute of Management \r",{"entities":[[0,30,"ORG"]]}],["08/2017 - 07/2018\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DATE"],[8,17,"DATE"]]}],["Bengaluru, India \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Machine Learning Algorithms, Advance Regression, Bayesian approach,\r",{"entities":[[0,16,"SKILLS"],[29,47,"METHODOLOGIES"],[49,66,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Analytics in Public policy, Artiﬁcial Intelligence. \r",{"entities":[[28,50,"SKILLS"]]}],["Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Bachelor of\r",{"entities":[[0,38,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Kalinga Institute of Industrial Technology \r",{"entities":[[0,42,"ORG"]]}],["07/2008 - 06/2012\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DATE"],[10,17,"DATE"]]}],["Bhubaneswar, India \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"GPE"]]}],["Senior Engineer \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Siemens \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"]]}],["09/2019 - Present\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DATE"]]}],["Bengaluru, India \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Training and supporting team on latest AI technologies. \r",{"entities":[[39,54,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["seminar/session on AI technology within and outside organization. \r",{"entities":[[19,39,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Requirement planning, resource management and task allocation. \r",{"entities":[[22,41,"SKILLS"]]}],["Siemens \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"]]}],["07/2012 - 09/2019\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DATE"],[10,17,"DATE"]]}],["Bengaluru, India \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Full stack developer in multiple projects. \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Full stack developer. Tools and\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["languages: Visual Studio C#, MS-Sql, TypeScript (JavaScript), WPF,\r",{"entities":[[11,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,26,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,35,"METHODOLOGIES"],[37,60,"METHODOLOGIES"],[62,66,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["WinForm, Python, Java, Web services. \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Machine Learning Algorithms \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"SKILLS"]]}],["Decision Tree, Random Forest, XGBoost, SVM, PCA,\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"METHODOLOGIES"],[15,28,"METHODOLOGIES"],[30,37,"METHODOLOGIES"],[39,42,"METHODOLOGIES"],[44,47,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["K-Means, Hierarchical Clustering, Density Clustering,\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[34,52,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Gaussian Mixture, Naïve Bayes. \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,29,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Statistics Learning Algorithms \r",{"entities":[[0,30,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Linear/Logistic regression. \r",{"entities":[[0,26,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Deep Learning Algorithms \r",{"entities":[[0,24,"SKILLS"]]}],["Neural Network, Convolution Neural Network,\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"METHODOLOGIES"],[16,42,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Recurrent Neural Network, Encoder-Decoder. \r",{"entities":[[0,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,42,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Shapely, Integrated gradients, Feature Importance,\r",{"entities":[[9,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[31,50,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Activation maximization, Unit testing. \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,37,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Time Series Analysis \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"SKILLS"]]}],["Exponential Smoothing, Holt's Linear Trend, Holt-\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"METHODOLOGIES"],[21,42,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Google Cloud Platform \r",{"entities":[[0,21,"SKILLS"]]}],["Transformation Pipeline, MLOps, Data Lake, Data\r",{"entities":[[0,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[32,41,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Warehouse. \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["SQL query \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Natural Language Processing \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Computer Vision \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Reinforcement Learning \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Software Design \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Requirement planning \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"SKILLS"]]}],["Data Structure \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"SKILLS"]]}],["07/2018 \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"DATE"]]}],["Published by academia - IIMB/DCAL. \r",{"entities":[[24,33,"ORG"]]}],[" (09/2020 - 12/2021)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"],[12,20,"DATE"]]}],["Ashok Leyland wants to leverage on the energy consumption data collected from\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"ORG"]]}],["engineering pipeline on Google Cloud Platform. Used Cloud Storage as data Lake,\r",{"entities":[[24,46,"SKILLS"],[69,78,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Data Fusion for transformation and Big query as warehouse. \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"METHODOLOGIES"],[35,44,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Used Kubeﬂow Sdk to automate end-to-end ML pipeline with custom google\r",{"entities":[[5,16,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Vertex AI was used to programmatically execute pipeline in\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["warehouse, execute model serving docker container, \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"METHODOLOGIES"],[33,49,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["adjusted r-square increased) and ﬁnally perform batch prediction. \r",{"entities":[[0,17,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Model was implemented as statistical learning with OLS, using Statsmodels.\r",{"entities":[[25,45,"SKILLS"],[51,54,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["adjusted r-square of 0.675. Residual analysis was positive. Outlier diagnostics was\r",{"entities":[[0,17,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,45,"SKILLS"]]}],[" (01/2019 - 03/2020)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"],[12,19,"DATE"]]}],["Worked closely with PLM to identify potential use case where AI could be leveraged\r",{"entities":[[20,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Created model to caption substation design using encoder-decoder architecture.\r",{"entities":[[49,77,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Network comprises of pretrained ResNet50 as encoder and LSTM as decoder, with\r",{"entities":[[32,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[56,60,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["cross entropy loss and Adam optimizer. \r",{"entities":[[0,13,"METHODOLOGIES"],[23,37,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Worked closely with PLM to identify potential use case where AI could be leveraged\r",{"entities":[[20,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" (10/2017 - 07/2018)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"],[12,19,"DATE"]]}],["Walmart Inc. allows customer to return product, within 90 days of purchase.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"]]}],["of revenue to company. Walmart would like to how much markdown should be\r",{"entities":[[14,22,"ORG"],[23,30,"ORG"]]}],["business perspective of problem. Performed exploratory data analysis on\r",{"entities":[[43,68,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Schema model (logical data model) with Sales Data and Returns Data as the main\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Proposed dynamic pricing of returned product based on inventories, shelf-life and\r",{"entities":[[9,24,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Average, Moving Average, Simple Exponential Smoothing, ARIMA. \r",{"entities":[[9,23,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,53,"METHODOLOGIES"],[55,61,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["select model based on AIC and RMSE, for diﬀerent product. \r",{"entities":[[22,25,"METHODOLOGIES"],[30,34,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Model was deployed on Power BI using SSAS Tabular model. \r",{"entities":[[22,30,"SKILLS"],[37,55,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" (02/2022 - Present)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"]]}],[" (04/2020 - 06/2020)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"],[12,19,"DATE"]]}],["Reinforcement Learning, Deep Q-Networks, Deep\r",{"entities":[[0,22,"SKILLS"],[24,39,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Udacity Computer Vision, Nano-degree.\r",{"entities":[[8,23,"SKILLS"]]}],[" (07/2018 - 09/2018)\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"DATE"],[12,19,"DATE"]]}],["Convolutional Neural Networks, Recurrent Neural Networks,\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[29,56,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Simultaneous Localization and Mapping. \r",{"entities":[[0,25,"METHODOLOGIES"],[30,37,"SKILLS"]]}],["Cooking \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"HOBBIES"]]}],["Ankush  Garg                       #339 , Old Housing Board Colony Sirsa Haryana | Emai l: ankush.20garg@gmail.com \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"NAME"],[42,80,"ADDRESS"],[91,114,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["                                                                                                                                 Phone : +91 -875 -051 -445 1 \r",{"entities":[[137,157,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["DCRUST Murthal | Haryana, IND  | B. Tech (EE) | Graduation Date: May 2015 CGPA: 7.79 \r",{"entities":[[17,29,"GPE"],[33,45,"EDUCATION"],[65,73,"DATE"]]}],["GRG  School  | Haryana,  IND  | XIIth in Non -Medical  | Graduation  Date:  Mar  2011  Marks  Percentage : 82 \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"ORG"],[15,28,"GPE"],[76,85,"DATE"]]}],["SBGSS School | Haryana, IND | Xth | Graduation Date: April 200 9 Marks Percentage: 84 \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[15,27,"GPE"],[53,64,"DATE"]]}],["Assistant  System  Engineer  | Tata  Consultancy  Services,  Noida,  IND  Mar  2016 - Mar  2017  \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"DESIGNATION"],[31,58,"ORG"],[61,72,"GPE"],[74,83,"DATE"],[86,95,"DATE"]]}],["System  Engineer  | Tata  Consultancy  Services,  Noida,  IND  Mar 2017 - Apr  2019  \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"DESIGNATION"],[20,47,"ORG"],[50,61,"GPE"],[63,71,"DATE"],[74,83,"DATE"]]}],["Software  Engineer  | Espire  Infolabs,  Gurgaon,  IND  Apr 2019 - Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"DESIGNATION"],[22,38,"ORG"],[41,54,"GPE"],[56,64,"DATE"]]}],["• Application  Software  & Other:  SharePoint  Online,  Share  Point  2010,  Visual  Studio  Code,  PowerApps,  Microsoft  Flow  (Power \r",{"entities":[[35,53,"METHODOLOGIES"],[56,74,"METHODOLOGIES"],[77,98,"METHODOLOGIES"],[100,109,"METHODOLOGIES"],[112,130,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Automate), Power BI, SPFx , Nintex Forms, Nintex Workflow, Jira \r",{"entities":[[11,19,"SKILLS"],[21,25,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[42,57,"METHODOLOGIES"],[57,63,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Technical Skills: CSOM, JSOM, Rest API, SharePoint Content Types, Content Type Hub, Master Pages \r",{"entities":[[20,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,30,"METHODOLOGIES"],[32,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[42,66,"METHODOLOGIES"],[68,84,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Programming Languages: Python, Typescript, JavaScript, JQuery, C# \r",{"entities":[[25,31,"SKILLS"],[33,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,56,"METHODOLOGIES"],[57,63,"METHODOLOGIES"],[65,66,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Front -End Web Technologies: HTML5  , CSS, JavaScript  \r",{"entities":[[31,36,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,44,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,55,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Support  of Intranet Portal  in SharePoint 2010  | TCS  Mar  2016 -Apr  2019  \r",{"entities":[[32,47,"METHODOLOGIES"],[51,54,"ORG"],[56,65,"DATE"],[66,76,"DATE"]]}],["• Used  Remedy tool for tickets and  incident tracking . \r",{"entities":[[8,19,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Development of Document Sharing Portal in  SharePoint Online  | TCS  Jun 2018 -Apr  2019  \r",{"entities":[[43,60,"METHODOLOGIES"],[64,67,"ORG"],[69,77,"DATE"],[78,88,"DATE"]]}],["• Development  of front -end  environment  in SharePoint  online.  \r",{"entities":[[46,64,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Used  Jira  for user  cases  and  tasks  for development.  \r",{"entities":[[8,12,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Worked  with  classic  pages  of SharePoint  and  integrating  scripts  in classic  pages.  \r",{"entities":[[35,45,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Created  Nintex  forms  and  associated  Nintex  workflow  for the different  content  types.  \r",{"entities":[[43,59,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Document Central Site | Espire Infolabs  May  2019 -Present  \r",{"entities":[[24,39,"ORG"],[41,50,"DATE"]]}],["• Created Task Manager app in  PowerApps.  \r",{"entities":[[31,40,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Developed  webpart  in SPFx  using  Typescript  and  PnP  and  deployed  it on modern  page.  \r",{"entities":[[25,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[38,48,"METHODOLOGIES"],[55,58,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Intranet Portal Site | Espire  Infolabs  May 2019 - Present  \r",{"entities":[[23,39,"ORG"],[41,49,"DATE"]]}],["• Developed Intranet portal site for Australian Client using OOTB webparts like quick links, Recent Documents, Highlighted Content etc. on \r",{"entities":[[61,74,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Created Reports using Power  BI. \r",{"entities":[[24,33,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Worked  in a completely  Agile  environment  and  used  Jira  tool  for sprints.  \r",{"entities":[[58,68,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• External  competency  in python  from  NPTEL  (IIT  Madras).  \r",{"entities":[[49,60,"ORG"]]}],["• Three  promotions  in 3.2 years  of experience  in TCS.  \r",{"entities":[[24,33,"EXPERIENCE"],[53,56,"ORG"]]}],["ARUN MENON  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"NAME"]]}],["DATA SCIENTIST | MACHINE LEARNING  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"DESIGNATION"],[17,33,"SKILLS"]]}],["arun.sivarag@gmail.com  | +91 9003037191  | LinkedIn   \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"EMAIL ID"],[26,40,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["An IT Professional  with 10 years of experience in Software development, turned to develop and grow interest in the field of \r",{"entities":[[25,33,"EXPERIENCE"],[51,71,"SKILLS"]]}],["Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning. Possess hands -on experience of writing codes in various programming languages \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"SKILLS"],[28,45,"SKILLS"],[103,114,"SKILLS"]]}],["and provide efficient solu tions to the target audience. Always intrigued working towards big data and enthusiastic about new \r",{"entities":[[90,98,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["challenges and opportunities. Excellent analytical thinking and written/verbal communication skills.  \r",{"entities":[[40,59,"SKILLS"],[64,92,"SKILLS"]]}],["Statistical Analysis  Missing values and Outliers | Univariate Analysis | Bi -Variate Analysis | \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"SKILLS"],[22,49,"METHODOLOGIES"],[52,71,"METHODOLOGIES"],[74,94,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Cross Validation | Hypothesis Testing | Predictive Analysis | Principal \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[19,37,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,59,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Component Analysis | Dimensionality Reduction  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"METHODOLOGIES"],[21,45,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Machine Learning  Classification | Regression | Clustering | De cision Trees | K -Means | \r",{"entities":[[18,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[35,45,"METHODOLOGIES"],[48,60,"METHODOLOGIES"],[61,76,"METHODOLOGIES"],[79,87,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Clustering  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"SKILLS"]]}],["Deep Learning  Image Classification | NLP  \r",{"entities":[[0,35,"SKILLS"],[38,41,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Full Stack Web Development  Front -end UI Designing | Client -side coding | Server -Side coding | Backend \r",{"entities":[[11,26,"SKILLS"],[28,51,"SKILLS"],[54,73,"SKILLS"],[76,95,"SKILLS"]]}],["database management | Services integration | ETL management  \r",{"entities":[[0,19,"SKILLS"],[45,59,"SKILLS"]]}],["Project Management  Requirements gathering | Planning | Client -centric deliverables | Agile \r",{"entities":[[87,92,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["methodologies | Time Management | Problem solving | Adaptability  \r",{"entities":[[16,31,"SKILLS"],[34,49,"SKILLS"]]}],["Python | ASP.net | C# | SQL | WCF | SSIS | Angular | JavaScript | HTML | CSS |  jQuery  \r",{"entities":[[0,6,"METHODOLOGIES"],[9,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[19,20,"METHODOLOGIES"],[24,29,"METHODOLOGIES"],[30,33,"METHODOLOGIES"],[36,40,"METHODOLOGIES"],[43,50,"METHODOLOGIES"],[53,63,"METHODOLOGIES"],[66,70,"METHODOLOGIES"],[73,76,"METHODOLOGIES"],[77,86,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["PGP AIML (P ost  Graduate Program in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning ) \r",{"entities":[[0,8,"EDUCATION"],[10,33,"EDUCATION"]]}],["The University  of Texas a t Austin  | Great Lakes Institu te of M anag emen t, Chennai  |2020 -2021  \r",{"entities":[[0,35,"ORG"],[39,78,"ORG"],[80,87,"ORG"]]}],["Bachelor  Of Engineering in  Electronics and Communication Engineering   \r",{"entities":[[0,70,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Asan Memorial C ollege of En gineering and  Tech nology , Anna Univer sity, Chennai  |2007 - 2011  \r",{"entities":[[0,55,"ORG"],[58,74,"ORG"],[76,83,"GPE"]]}],["Unlimited Innovations India Pvt Ltd, Chennai  \r",{"entities":[[0,35,"ORG"],[37,44,"GPE"]]}],["TECHNICAL LEAD, Feb 2019 – Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"DESIGNATION"],[16,24,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["● Handling large data and utilizing high quality normalization techniques with SQL queries to pre -process the data and \r",{"entities":[[79,90,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["● Involved in creating WCF services and batch jobs to get the source data from third party resources which are to be \r",{"entities":[[23,35,"SKILLS"]]}],["used by the data analysts and build Web applications to present the data in UI as per the requirement.  \r",{"entities":[[12,25,"SKILLS"],[76,78,"SKILLS"]]}],["● Involved in ga thering and analysing the requirements from the client and based on the analysis provide client -centric \r",{"entities":[[29,38,"SKILLS"]]}],["Sagarsoft India Pvt Ltd / Sagarsoft INC., Stamford CT - USA   \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"],[26,40,"ORG"],[56,59,"GPE"]]}],["Senior .NET Associa te, Jul 2018 - Jan 2019  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"DESIGNATION"],[24,32,"DATE"],[35,43,"DATE"]]}],["SQL Server.  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["errors and troubleshooting the web applications and resolving the issues by debugging the .NET modules of the \r",{"entities":[[90,94,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Cognizant Technology Solutions India Pvt Ltd / Cognizant Technology Solutions US Corp, Stamford CT - USA  \r",{"entities":[[0,44,"ORG"],[47,85,"ORG"],[101,104,"GPE"]]}],["Associate, Nov 2011 - Jul 2018  \r",{"entities":[[0,9,"DESIGNATION"],[11,19,"DATE"],[22,30,"DATE"]]}],["● Developed end to end web applications single -handedly using .Net Framework (C#, ASP.Net , ADO.Net). Utilized most \r",{"entities":[[63,77,"METHODOLOGIES"],[79,80,"METHODOLOGIES"],[83,90,"METHODOLOGIES"],[93,100,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["of the UI tools/ languages like JavaScript, jQuery, Knockout JS, HTML and CSS to create web pages.  \r",{"entities":[[32,42,"METHODOLOGIES"],[44,50,"METHODOLOGIES"],[52,63,"METHODOLOGIES"],[65,69,"METHODOLOGIES"],[74,77,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Identified potential loan customers for Thera Bank using classification techniques. Compared models built with Logistic \r",{"entities":[[57,83,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Regression and KNN algorithm to select the best performing one.  \r",{"entities":[[0,10,"METHODOLOGIES"],[15,28,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Skills and Tools  - Logistic Regression, KNN, Classification  \r",{"entities":[[20,39,"METHODOLOGIES"],[41,44,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,60,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Skills and Tools  - Collaborative Filtering, Recommender Systems, Python  \r",{"entities":[[20,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,64,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Implementing an Image classification neural network to classify Street House View Numbers   \r",{"entities":[[16,36,"METHODOLOGIES"],[37,51,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["a simple image classification pipeline based on the k -Nearest Neighbour and a deep neural network.  \r",{"entities":[[52,72,"METHODOLOGIES"],[79,98,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Skills and Tools  - Neural Networks, Deep Learning, Keras, Image Recognition  \r",{"entities":[[20,35,"SKILLS"],[37,50,"SKILLS"],[52,57,"METHODOLOGIES"],[59,76,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Sentiment analysis   \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"SKILLS"]]}],["Skills and Tools - RNN, Word embedding, LSTM, Classificatio n \r",{"entities":[[19,22,"METHODOLOGIES"],[22,38,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,44,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Personal Profile  Name  Ankit Pratik  Phone  +91 -962018313   \r",{"entities":[[24,36,"NAME"],[45,59,"MOBILE NO."]]}],[" D.O.B  28th April 1994  Email  ankitpratik1994@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[8,23,"DOB"],[32,57,"EMAIL ID"]]}],[" Address  102, Suddha Shelters, Bilekahalli, Bengaluru, Karnataka  - 560076  \r",{"entities":[[10,75,"ADDRESS"]]}],["Total Experience of 4.7  years  in Software Development. Presently associated with  Levtech Consulting \r",{"entities":[[20,30,"EXPERIENCE"],[84,102,"ORG"]]}],["Services India Pvt. Ltd.  as Senior Technical Consultant  for Dynamics 365 . \r",{"entities":[[0,24,"ORG"],[29,56,"DESIGNATION"],[62,74,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Strong Technical Knowledge of D365 for Operations (Extensions, Delegates, Model \r",{"entities":[[32,36,"SKILLS"],[65,74,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["• Excellent team player with problem -solving capabilities.  \r",{"entities":[[12,23,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.  \r",{"entities":[[15,56,"SKILLS"]]}],["• Adroit in Problem  impact analysis skill and open to adapt to  new technologies.  \r",{"entities":[[12,42,"SKILLS"]]}],["Work Experience  Levtech Consulting Services  → August 2018 – Till Date\r",{"entities":[[17,44,"ORG"],[48,59,"DATE"]]}],[" Senior Technical Consultant  (Dynamics 365)  \r",{"entities":[[1,28,"DESIGNATION"],[31,43,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Tectura Japan KK  → July  2017 – July 2018\r",{"entities":[[1,17,"ORG"],[21,31,"DATE"],[34,43,"DATE"]]}],[" Technical Consultant  (Dynamics 365)  \r",{"entities":[[1,21,"DESIGNATION"],[24,37,"SKILLS"]]}],[" L&T Infotech  → June 2015 – July 2017\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"ORG"],[17,26,"DATE"],[29,38,"DATE"]]}],[" Software Associate  (Microsoft Dynamics AX)  \r",{"entities":[[1,19,"DESIGNATION"],[22,43,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Educational Profile  B.E in CSE from NMIT, Bangalore  8.4 CGPA  \r",{"entities":[[21,31,"EDUCATION"],[37,41,"ORG"],[43,52,"GPE"]]}],[" Secondary School  Examination  84.4 %  \r",{"entities":[[1,17,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Certifications  .Net Development  \r",{"entities":[[16,32,"SKILLS"]]}],["Tools & Software  Microsoft D ynamics  → Dynamics 365, AX 2012 (R3),  \r",{"entities":[[55,62,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" MS Tools    → MS – Office, Visual Studio  \r",{"entities":[[15,26,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,41,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Database  → SQL  \r",{"entities":[[13,16,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" ANKITPRATIK1994@GMAI L.COM                      9620183130  \r",{"entities":[[1,27,"EMAIL ID"],[49,59,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["ANKIT PRATIK  \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"NAME"]]}],["Microsoft Dynamics AX Technical Consultant  \r",{"entities":[[0,42,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["  Implementation (AX 2012 R3 )   → L& T In fotech, Ramaco  \r",{"entities":[[35,49,"ORG"],[49,57,"ORG"]]}],["Projects type w orked on Implementation (AX 2012 R3, D365 FinOps ) \r",{"entities":[[41,51,"SKILLS"],[53,66,"SKILLS"]]}],["Place : Bangalore        Ankit Pratik  \r",{"entities":[[8,17,"GPE"],[25,37,"GPE"]]}],[" ANKITPRATIK1994@GMAI L.COM                      9620183130  \r",{"entities":[[1,27,"GPE"],[49,59,"MOBILE NO."]]}],[" AKHIL NAIR  \r",{"entities":[[1,11,"NAME"]]}],["+91 7045206253  \r",{"entities":[[0,14,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["akhilnair498@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["STANDARD  BOARD/UNIVERSITY  PERCENTAGE/GPA /GRADE  MONTH & \r",{"entities":[[0,26,"EDUCATION"]]}],["S.S.C  MAHARASHTRA  76.73%  MARCH \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"]]}],["2011  ST. MARY’S \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"DATE"],[6,16,"ORG"]]}],["H.S.C  MAHARASHTRA  57.33%  FEBRUARY \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"EDUCATION"],[28,36,"DATE"]]}],["2013  R.K. TALREJA \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"DATE"]]}],["B.A. (ENGLISH \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"EDUCATION"]]}],["LITERATURE)  MUMBAI  GRADE ‘B’  APRIL 2017  RAMNIRANJAN \r",{"entities":[[32,42,"DATE"]]}],[" I have worked  as an English Tutor for private  coaching  classes for two years  (May 2017  – May 2019). I \r",{"entities":[[72,81,"EXPERIENCE"],[84,92,"DATE"],[96,104,"DATE"]]}],[" I have edited and proofread articles  as a freelancer for Dorf Ketal.  \r",{"entities":[[45,55,"DESIGNATION"],[60,70,"ORG"]]}],[" At present, working as a Content Writer  and Editor at Inkwood Research . \r",{"entities":[[27,41,"DESIGNATION"],[47,53,"DESIGNATION"],[57,73,"ORG"]]}],[" Teaching  \r",{"entities":[[2,10,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Writing (Research, Editing, Proofreading)  \r",{"entities":[[11,19,"SKILLS"],[21,28,"SKILLS"]]}],[" MS Word  \r",{"entities":[[2,9,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["prizes for poetry, short story, letter writing etc.  \r",{"entities":[[0,46,"AWARDS AND ACHIVEMENTS"]]}],[" Reading  \r",{"entities":[[2,9,"HOBBIES"]]}],[" Writing  \r",{"entities":[[2,9,"HOBBIES"]]}],[" Name     : AKHIL MURALI NAIR  \r",{"entities":[[13,30,"NAME"]]}],[" Address    : Shree Krishna Niwas, Room No.2, New Jimmi Baugh, Kalyan East.   \r",{"entities":[[15,75,"ADDRESS"]]}],[" Date of Birth    : 7th January, 1996  \r",{"entities":[[21,38,"DOB"]]}],[" Languages Known    : English, Hindi, Marathi and Malayalam  \r",{"entities":[[23,30,"LANGUAGES"],[32,37,"LANGUAGES"],[39,46,"LANGUAGES"],[51,60,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["Place:  MUMBAI                                                                                                                           AKHIL NAIR  \r",{"entities":[[5,14,"GPE"],[137,147,"NAME"]]}],["AMIT MAHADIK  \r",{"entities":[[0,12,"NAME"]]}],["Contact: +91 -9821833848; +91 -9820259228  | Skype Id:  amitm3012  \r",{"entities":[[9,24,"MOBILE NO."],[26,41,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["E-Mail:  amit_mahadik@rediffmail.com; amitmahadik78@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[9,36,"EMAIL ID"],[38,61,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["Address:  Ashtavinayak Gruh Sankul -2, Adai, Near Sect -9, New Panvel, Navi Mumbai – 410206\r",{"entities":[[7,91,"ADDRESS"]]}],["A result -oriented professional with 16 years of rich experience in:  \r",{"entities":[[37,45,"EXPERIENCE"]]}],["Strategic Planning & Control   Sales and Marketing    Business Development  \r",{"entities":[[0,18,"SKILLS"],[21,50,"SKILLS"],[54,74,"SKILLS"]]}],["Training & Dev elopment   Partner Management/Engagement   Team Management  \r",{"entities":[[58,73,"SKILLS"]]}],["Key Accounts Management   Brand Promotion     Market Research  \r",{"entities":[[26,41,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Gained experience in feasibility analysis of the potential customers, market trends analysis, strategic decision support, \r",{"entities":[[23,43,"SKILLS"],[72,94,"SKILLS"],[96,122,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Innovative marketing instincts, insight, judgment and ability to work & succeed on tough deals  \r",{"entities":[[13,32,"SKILLS"],[34,41,"SKILLS"],[56,96,"SKILLS"]]}],["MicroW orld Software Services Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai       Aug 2014 - Present  \r",{"entities":[[0,39,"ORG"],[54,62,"DATE"]]}],["As Business Development Manager - Enterprise Sales  \r",{"entities":[[3,31,"DESIGNATION"]]}],[" Interfacing with E nd Customers, Creating opportunities for New customer Acquisition, cross -selling & up -selling of Cyber \r",{"entities":[[66,86,"SKILLS"],[88,102,"SKILLS"],[105,116,"SKILLS"]]}],["Point Protection Security solutions, Cloud Edition , Remote Monitoring & Management, eBack -up, Email Server Security, MDM , \r",{"entities":[[17,35,"METHODOLOGIES"],[37,50,"METHODOLOGIES"],[53,83,"METHODOLOGIES"],[85,94,"METHODOLOGIES"],[119,122,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Vulnerability Assessment, Penetration Testing, Dynam ic Application Security Testing ) & Professional Services (VAPT , DAST )  \r",{"entities":[[0,24,"METHODOLOGIES"],[26,45,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Managing business operations across Mumbai, Pune, Rest of Maharashtra (ROM) and specific customers at Goa & Gujarat  \r",{"entities":[[38,44,"GPE"],[46,50,"GPE"],[104,107,"GPE"],[110,117,"GPE"]]}],[" Driving existing large accounts like C -Edge technologies  \r",{"entities":[[39,59,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Major New Customers generated: Aditya Birla Group, TCS iON  (IRM Project) , ADAG (Reliance Entertainment), 3i -Infotech, \r",{"entities":[[33,52,"ORG"],[53,60,"ORG"],[84,106,"ORG"],[109,121,"ORG"]]}],["Urban Cooperative Banks across Mumbai, ROM & Goa,  Government: M antralya Bank, Mahatransco, Maha -Online , Educational \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"],[31,37,"GPE"]]}],["Ingram Micro India Ltd., Mumbai         Dec 2010 - Aug 2014  \r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"],[25,31,"GPE"],[40,48,"DATE"],[51,59,"DATE"]]}],["As Deputy Manager - Sales - Strategic Account  \r",{"entities":[[3,17,"DESIGNATION"],[20,25,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Handled  all end to end product portfolio of Ingram Micro : (Major Product Brands)  : Software (MicroSoft, Symantec, McAfee, \r",{"entities":[[47,59,"ORG"]]}],[" Major clients Handled: TCS, Godrej & Boyce, Tech Mahindra, CMC,  BT, CMS Computers  and  other  System Integrat ion partners  \r",{"entities":[[25,28,"ORG"],[28,36,"ORG"],[39,44,"ORG"],[46,59,"ORG"],[71,84,"ORG"]]}],["Tikona Digital Networks Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai        May 2010 - Nov 2010  \r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"],[35,41,"GPE"],[49,57,"DATE"],[60,68,"DATE"]]}],["As Key Account Manager - Enterprise Sales  \r",{"entities":[[3,22,"DESIGNATION"]]}],[" Accountable for selling the solutions (wireless leased line/ bandwidth) to enterprise and SMB customers in Navi Mumbai region  \r",{"entities":[[109,120,"GPE"]]}],[" Successfully bagged orders from Logistics Group and SMB segments in Navi Mumbai territory  \r",{"entities":[[70,81,"GPE"]]}],["Verve Communications Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai         Dec 2009 - May 2010  \r",{"entities":[[0,30,"ORG"],[30,38,"GPE"],[47,55,"DATE"],[58,66,"DATE"]]}],["As Business Development Manager  \r",{"entities":[[3,31,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["HCL Infosystems Ltd., Mumbai          Jun 2008 – Oct 2009  \r",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"],[22,28,"GPE"],[38,46,"DATE"],[49,57,"DATE"]]}],["As Key Account Executive – HCL Infinet Division  \r",{"entities":[[3,24,"DESIGNATION"],[27,30,"ORG"]]}],["Data Center Services  of HCL Infinet to corporate and enterprise accounts  \r",{"entities":[[25,28,"ORG"]]}],[" Successfully bagged orders from corporate accounts like Essel Propack Group  \r",{"entities":[[58,77,"ORG"]]}],["Rolta India Ltd., Mumbai          Jul 2006 – Jun 2008  \r",{"entities":[[0,16,"ORG"],[18,24,"GPE"],[34,42,"DATE"],[45,53,"DATE"]]}],["As Sales Executive (L1) – Sales & Marketing Division  \r",{"entities":[[3,18,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Vijay Sabre Safety Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai         Jul 2004 – Jul 2006  \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"ORG"],[30,36,"ORG"]]}],["As Sales Engineer - Disaster Management Equipment  \r",{"entities":[[3,19,"DESIGNATION"]]}],[" Managed customer segments like Fire Departments across India: Lucknow, Bhopal, Delhi, Ahmedabad, Hyderabad; Fire \r",{"entities":[[64,71,"GPE"],[73,79,"GPE"],[81,86,"GPE"],[88,97,"GPE"],[99,108,"GPE"]]}],["Brigades across Maharashtra;  Railways; Coastguard; Security Services   \r",{"entities":[[16,27,"GPE"]]}],["2004  MMS (Master of Management Studies) from Pillai Institute of Management Studies & Research (PIMSR), New Panvel, \r",{"entities":[[11,39,"EDUCATION"],[46,95,"ORG"],[103,115,"GPE"]]}],["2001  BE (Bachelor of Engineering) - Chemical Engineering  from Tatyasaheb Kore Inst itute of Engineering and \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"DATE"],[6,34,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Technology (TKIET) Warananagar, Shivaji University; Distinction  \r",{"entities":[[32,50,"ORG"]]}],["o Pro-Degree in Data Science (Software :R, Python, SAS, Tableau) (through Distance Learning course)  \r",{"entities":[[2,28,"EDUCATION"],[40,41,"METHODOLOGIES"],[51,54,"METHODOLOGIES"],[56,63,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["o Diploma in Process Engineering (through part time  course )  \r",{"entities":[[2,32,"EDUCATION"]]}],["o Diploma in Multimedia & Certification course in C, C++ in year 1999  during BE  \r",{"entities":[[2,23,"EDUCATION"],[50,51,"METHODOLOGIES"],[53,56,"METHODOLOGIES"],[65,69,"DATE"]]}],[" Worked on  software during MMS:  SPSS (Statistical Package for the Social Sciences)  \r",{"entities":[[29,84,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Worked on software during BE:  ASPEN Plus (Advanced System for Pro cess Engineering),  AutoCAD   \r",{"entities":[[33,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[45,85,"METHODOLOGIES"],[89,96,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["o Industrial training at Sugar factory during BE  \r",{"entities":[[2,21,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Date of Birth   December 30, 1978  \r",{"entities":[[16,33,"DOB"]]}],["Languages Known  English, Hindi and Marathi   \r",{"entities":[[17,24,"LANGUAGES"],[26,31,"LANGUAGES"],[36,43,"LANGUAGES"]]}],["Akshay Douglas Gudinho  \r",{"entities":[[0,6,"NAME"]]}],["Phone: 996 -729 -0062  Email Addr ess: akshaygudinho@gmail.com  \r",{"entities":[[7,21,"MOBILE NO."],[39,62,"EMAIL ID"]]}],["MyAdvo.com, Legal Content W riter, January 2020 - August  2020 . \r",{"entities":[[12,33,"DESIGNATION"],[35,47,"DATE"],[50,64,"DATE"]]}],["Young Bharatiya, Research Assistant, November 2019 - January 2020.  \r",{"entities":[[0,15,"ORG"],[17,35,"DESIGNATION"],[37,50,"DATE"],[53,65,"DATE"]]}],["Dhruve Liladhar & Company, Mumbai, India, Advocate Associate, Debt Recovery, Property and \r",{"entities":[[0,25,"ORG"],[27,40,"GPE"],[42,60,"DESIGNATION"]]}],["Arbitration, May 2019 - October 2019.  \r",{"entities":[[11,21,"DATE"],[24,36,"DATE"]]}],["Bar Membership : Admitted to the Bar Council of Maharashtra and Goa, August 2019.  \r",{"entities":[[69,80,"DATE"]]}],["Symbiosis Law School, Pune: Bachelor of Laws (LL.B.), 2016 -2019.  \r",{"entities":[[28,52,"EDUCATION"]]}],["St. Xavier’s College Autonomous, Mumbai : Bachelor of Arts: Political Science, 2013 -2016.  \r",{"entities":[[42,58,"EDUCATION"],[60,77,"EDUCATION"],[79,89,"DATE"]]}],["authored by Dr. D. Ganesh  Kumar.  \r",{"entities":[[12,32,"DATE"]]}],["Rawlsian  Applic ations  - Co-autho red by Dr. D. Ganesh  Kuma r. \r",{"entities":[[43,65,"NAME"]]}],["between  the  Constitution  and  Personal  Laws  - Co-autho red by Dr. D. Ganesh  Kuma r. \r",{"entities":[[67,88,"NAME"]]}],["Co- autho red by Dr. D. Ganesh  Kumar.   \r",{"entities":[[17,37,"NAME"]]}],["RDIAS,  GGSIPU , DELHI  | MASTER IN MANAGEMENT  2012 – 14 New Delhi  \r",{"entities":[[26,46,"EDUCATION"],[62,67,"GPE"]]}],["Special ization – Marketing and Human  Resource  \r",{"entities":[[0,47,"EDUCATION"]]}],["INSTITUTE OF INSTRUMENTATION ENGINEERING  | BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY  \r",{"entities":[[0,43,"ORG"],[44,66,"EDUCATION"]]}],["Specialization – Electronics and Instrumentation (E&I ) 2004  – 08  Kuru kshetra  \r",{"entities":[[0,53,"EDUCATION"]]}],["CHEGG  INDIA  PVT.LTD.  |TEAM  LEAD   Apr,19  – Oct, 19 New Delhi , India  \r",{"entities":[[0,22,"ORG"],[24,35,"DESIGNATION"],[38,44,"DATE"],[48,55,"DATE"],[56,73,"GPE"]]}],[" Led  a team of 5 associates  for email marketing, automation campaigns, HTML templates, creative s, content etc.  \r",{"entities":[[35,50,"METHODOLOGIES"],[52,72,"METHODOLOGIES"],[74,88,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Handled social media channels for Chegg India and run campaigns for lead generation and engagement  \r",{"entities":[[36,47,"ORG"]]}],[" Worked on  CRM  tool  (ZOHO CRM)  and  data visualization  tool (DOMO)  for  Continuous Improvement  \r",{"entities":[[13,22,"METHODOLOGIES"],[25,33,"METHODOLOGIES"],[41,72,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Increased expert engagement and activation via SMS and Wha tsApp marketing  \r",{"entities":[[57,76,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["BURDA  MEDIA  INDIA(  CLIENT : MICROSOFT ) |ASSO CIATE CAMPAIGN MANAGER                                                        OCT,18-JAN,19                    NOIDA , INDIA  \r",{"entities":[[0,19,"ORG"],[43,71,"DESIGNATION"],[160,173,"GPE"]]}],[" Planning and executing marketing campaigns for Micros oft India (MSN)  \r",{"entities":[[49,59,"ORG"]]}],[" Campaign reporting using Power BI  \r",{"entities":[[27,35,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["ELI  RESEARCH INDIA PVT. LTD. |MARKETING EXECUTIVE                                                                                                           MAY,15-JUL, 18               FARI DABAD , INDIA  \r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"],[30,50,"DESIGNATION"],[186,204,"GPE"]]}],[" Lead generation via email mark eting, social media  marketing, affiliate marketing  \r",{"entities":[[22,38,"METHODOLOGIES"],[40,63,"METHODOLOGIES"],[65,84,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" A/B testing, list hygiene, data management, lead scoring, lead management  \r",{"entities":[[2,13,"METHODOLOGIES"],[15,27,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,58,"METHODOLOGIES"],[60,75,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Worked on  various email marketing tool s (HubSpot, Eloqua, Marketo, Mailchimp etc. ) \r",{"entities":[[45,52,"METHODOLOGIES"],[54,60,"METHODOLOGIES"],[62,69,"METHODOLOGIES"],[69,80,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Rep orting via G oogle analytics and improving campaign metrics  \r",{"entities":[[17,34,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" SEO activities, keyword research , competitor analysis, blogs and content optimization  \r",{"entities":[[2,16,"METHODOLOGIES"],[18,34,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],[" Google ad s campaigns  \r",{"entities":[[2,23,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["DGM INDIA  PVT.LTD.  |MARKETING EXECUTIVE                                                                                                             AUG, 14-JAN, 15                NEW DELHI , INDIA  \r",{"entities":[[0,19,"ORG"],[21,41,"DESIGNATION"],[181,198,"GPE"]]}],[" Affiliate management, publisher onboarding and campaign execution  \r",{"entities":[[2,22,"SKILLS"],[49,67,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Strong underst anding of affiliate management tool HasOffers  \r",{"entities":[[53,62,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["RATTAN  POLYCHEM   PVT.LTD. |BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT EXECUTIVE                                                               JAN, 10-JUL, 12              FARIDA BAD , INDIA  \r",{"entities":[[0,27,"ORG"],[28,59,"DESIGNATION"],[151,169,"GPE"]]}],["WIPRO  LTD. | ASSOCIATE                                                                                                                                                      JUNE , 2008 -DEC, 08      NEW DELHI , INDIA  \r",{"entities":[[0,11,"ORG"],[14,177,"DESIGNATION"],[199,216,"GPE"]]}],[" 8 years  of professional expe rience in digital marketing  \r",{"entities":[[1,8,"EXPERIENCE"],[41,58,"SKILLS"]]}],[" Advanced digital ma rketing certificate from IIT, Delhi  \r",{"entities":[[46,56,"ORG"]]}],[" Maste r in Management, HubSpot certified marketer   Abhinav Sharm a \r",{"entities":[[1,22,"EDUCATION"]]}],["abhinavsharma2416 @gmail.com |     +9181 78000860  \r",{"entities":[[0,28,"EMAIL ID"],[35,49,"MOBILE NO."]]}],[" Strategic innovation, digital marketing and business analytics  (SIDMBA)  certificate from IIT, New Delhi (2019)  \r",{"entities":[[93,107,"MOBILE NO."]]}],["SKILLS  – MS Office Suite /Excel , Email marketing  automation , Marketing Planning, Digital Marketing, WordP ress , Canva , Survey \r",{"entities":[[10,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[35,62,"SKILLS"],[65,83,"SKILLS"],[85,102,"SKILLS"],[104,114,"METHODOLOGIES"],[117,122,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["Monkey , Google analytics , DOMO , Power BI , ZOHO , HTML, CSS , Basic understanding of R, Python, SPSS  \r",{"entities":[[9,25,"METHODOLOGIES"],[28,32,"METHODOLOGIES"],[35,43,"METHODOLOGIES"],[46,50,"METHODOLOGIES"],[53,57,"METHODOLOGIES"],[59,62,"METHODOLOGIES"],[88,89,"METHODOLOGIES"],[99,103,"METHODOLOGIES"]]}],["LANGUAGES  – English  (Native Proficiency), Hindi  (Mother tongue)  \r",{"entities":[[13,20,"LANGUAGES"],[44,49,"LANGUAGES"]]}]]}